What's the deal with airplane peanuts?
That was one of the best rants I've ever
heard in my life. Yeah, that's
fantastic. When it comes to going on
wild podcast rants, nobody does it
better than Tim Dylan. He's the Michael
Jordan of the rant. And these are seven
of the funniest rants from recent
episodes of the Tim Dylan Show. Starting
off with the Door Dash conversation from
episode 437. Making four payments to
cover three tacos on Tuesday sounds
complicated because it is, said Adam
Russ, director of financial services at
the Consumer Federation of America and
Advocacy Group. I wouldn't characterize
this as a solution. It's a fintech
innovation that creates problems. Hey,
Adam, off. We're hungry and broke. Why
not charge it? You people that go, why'd
you go bankrupt? You go, Door Dash. I
went I ran up I owe 80,000 to Door Dash.
We're going to run into that. People are
gonna go, I owe I owe
$70,000 to Door Dash because I charged
food for the last three years to
survive. Now I'm on disability because
I've eaten so much Door Dash I can't
even participate in the workforce. So
now I'm in a scooter that needs to be
paid for by disability and I owe
$75,000 for Door Dash. But by the way, a
lot of people and I get I've been in
that position position where you just
don't have theing money. People don't
have the money. That's what it is.
People need to eat. They don't have the
money, you know? I mean, that what are
you gonna do? You could go to a store, I
guess, and cook it. That's not American.
It's not American. Think about being
broke and cooking. How depressing that
is. Think about being poor and in your
kitchen with the thing like this with
the pan. It's not American. America is
about being a delusional
psychopath. It's like that's what it's
about. It's not about being a rational
person that makes America's about being
a a nut job all the time. So like you
order burritos, you charge them, you
scream and yell in your house, you live
stream to know
howing you you coach, you become a life
coach, you tell them that they don't
know how to be like it's all about the
hustle. It's about the grind. They can't
see that you're living in squalor, your
own filth. You know, you're like, "Yeah,
yeah, man. I'm going to crush you today.
Monday coffee. Yeah, the coffee. I want
the coffee in my mouth. And then you go
nuts and then you order a burrito and
then you charge it and then you're
completely you're 40 grand in debt. You
try to change your name. You cut your
[__] off. You throw it in the street.
You become trans. You're like, "I don't
owe that money." You go, "I think you do
it." You go, "Stop dead naming me." You
attack a TSA agent. You bite him in the
neck at LaGuardia. That's what being an
American is. It's not making eggs in
Europe. That what? That's not it. Being
an American is about going into debt,
developing an alternative persona,
becoming trans, and then attacking a TSA
agent. I think the thing about Casey
Anthony that we all have to remember is
she made one mistake. And we can't I
don't think we want to live in a country
where, and I've said this before on the
show, you kill one child and then it's
like, "All right, you're done." I still
want to hear what she has to say about
woman's rights. Call me a nut. Call me a
nut. Call me a nut to my face. That's
fine. You can think sticks and stones
may break my bones, but I like Casey
Anthony. I don't know how it goes. The
point is this. What did she do? She put
her daughter in a backpack and threw her
in the lake. Listen folks, it was a long
time ago and I'm not gonna hold it
against her. What does she have to say
about the women's rights and the privacy
is very interesting. I'm a known person.
I get it. Sometimes I'm recognized I'm
eating a frozen yogurt during the winter
and it's very strange. It's odd when
someone sees you in Canada eating ice
cream in the freezing cold and they go,
"Oh, that's that's a horrible choice.
What a monster you are." So, I get it.
The whole privacy thing is a problem.
Now, what did this woman do again? She
put put their her daughter in a food
processor. Now, that's not good. And I
would never say I would never defend.
But here's the only thing I would say. I
would
say,
"Hey, things get heated just because
this mother lied about literally
everything. I want to hear what she has
to say about the LGBTQ community. I want
to I want advocates. Even if they've
killed their kids, I do. I even if you
dispose of your daughter's body in a
wooded area, I want you to advocate for
women and me in the LGBTQ community.
There's nothing wrong. And about the
right to privacy. Isn't that funny?
She's go banging on about the right to
privacy. I mean, cuz it is disgusting in
this country now. What's happened?
Because here's what here's how bad it's
gotten in this country. You cannot
publicly kill your child and be left
alone. That's how bad it's gotten.
You make a reservation at the steakhouse
and you get some looks at the bar just
because you killed your daughter and
left her in a wooded area. Ellie needs
to be run by somebody who goes, "We have
a you're the gender you want to be." But
then also kill that fish. Kill the fish.
Hit it with a bat. Bludge in that fish.
Take the fish out and hit it with a bat
in the head and then get the water.
Steal the water. Steal it from Lake Me.
Steal. This is Los Angeles. This is not
an honest place. Steal, kill that fish
if we do not have politicians that can
kill a fish. What is all this woke [__]
for if you can't then go and do the cold
hard [__] you need to do? You should be
telling people crap and then stealing
water. That's the whole point. Tell
them, "Look, Batman's trans. Steal the
water. Steal the water. These houses are
worth a hundred million dollars. They're
going to burn down the fish. Get Rick
Caruso in there now. He made that little
Palisades mall. And the Grove. The
Grove's got a little train that goes
around it. Stop importing these failed
comedy writer communist losers that want
everything to burn cuz no one will read
their spec script about pickle ball. Get
some hard operators back. Batman's
trance. Did you steal all the water off?
Kill people. Start killing them again.
Do the control burns. Who gives a if
they're
mad? Who cares if Greta Thunderberg
doesn't like it? Doesn't matter. Make a
movie about that dumb [__] There's
ways to get on her good side. Bring that
Swedish freak in and make a movie about
her her shenanigans. Keep your mouth
shut about the stolen water. You want a
movie or not, you freak. Put on your
wooden shoes and put on your clogs. Get
over here. We'll make a film about you.
You keep your mouth shut. If LA is
unwilling to bring that type of
politician back, we're If these people
can't get tough with these interest
groups, we're if you can't tell people
it's unreasonable to have homeless
people running around you with gas cans,
I don't care what you think. I don't
care what you think in Silverlake. It's
a [__] all It's a dump. Nobody moved to
LA to live in Brooklyn with failures.
It's a dump. The east side sucks except
for Pasadena and Aladena, which I do
like. But we're new. Not taking edicts
from Echo Park. No, no, no. It was
called Beverly Hills 90210. You know
what it wasn'ting called? Eagle Rock
90210. Enough. Bring hard operators
back.
Cynical
craven people that will do what needs to
be done or the entire city will die. You
can't have people running around
psychotic, lighting things on fire. You
cannot have any preparation. You can't
have this boy [__] who lives on a
vineyard who who's he said these
interest groups own him. They own him.
You should be lying to them. You should
be saying one thing and doing another.
That's the point. That is the point.
Kill the fish. Oh, the fish is going to
go extinct. Well, now guess what? The
palisades has gone extinct. You chose
the fish over these white with their
fake hats. Where are they going to go?
Where are these [__] in their hats
going to go? That's the whole point of
our country is to be a [__] in a freak
hat. You know, there's a lot of meanings
of life, but one of the meanings of life
is to figure it out. To figure out how
to just have food and shelter. You need
you have basic needs that need to get
met. And sometimes you meet like no
matter what you end up doing, there's
going to be periods of your life that
you're going to work at places you don't
like. You know, this is what's going to
happen. you're not ev everybody's not
going to be uh I don't know uh the
people on Stranger Things those kids
like and they'll they're going to pay
late they're going to pay later they get
to pay later everyone pays everyone you
don't get out without paying you know
what I'm saying and and a lot of people
might disagree with me is that a a
deadend corporate gig where you're not
too low and you're not too high and
you're just kind of riding in the middle
and you're going uh you got a couple of
free tickets to the game you're taking
some client. He's a real schmuck, but
you know, he might reup with you. You
realize that's it. That is every you did
it. You did it because the war the world
is war and hell and famine and chaos and
you know or or people take an iasa in
their Rolls-Royce try to figure out how
deep is it? How do I I need to
actualize? But that's what it comes down
to. So when you look at the state of
chaos, it's all over the world. The idea
that you have some boring dead-end
corporate job is actually quite an
accomplishment. Not only of you, but of
the people around you. Yes or yes. Be
happy with those things. Fight for them.
Fight for the office. We're going back.
We're going back. We're go. Where's that
energy? It's all for Israel and the
Palestine. Where's the energy to go back
into the office to crawl back into it?
Crawl into it. We're going back. We're
going back.
Protest. Get your fat ass back in the
office cuz Deb is a sick [__] and you
want to tell someone about it. You I'm
tell your life will not get better.
Fight for this. No one's going to listen
to me. God, they'll play this years from
now. years from now after the people in
this town have had me killed. Years from
now, someone will hear this and they go,
"God, he was right. God, he was right.
We should have fought for the shitty
little deli in the basement of the
building. We should have fought for our
office. We should have fought for the
breakroom. We should have fought for it
for civilization. We should have fought
when we had the chance. We didn't cuz we
were all pompous and we all thought we
were better than that and we didn't need
it. We didn't need to see each other in
the flesh or talk to each other. Life
was a series of gigs or schemes. Jobs
were for
losers. Schemes were better. Gigs were
better. Even though they only enriched
the [__] apps on our phones and kept
us on a perpetual wheel, offered us
nothing in the way of cohesive social
environments. We all became lonely
freaks in our cars, our houses, our
apartments on messenger bikes, task
rabbit showing up, installing a TV, and
then leaving all of this stuff. We
didn't fight for the great American
office. the great deadend job. The great
middle class mediocre God, I wish I
hading applied myself in college and I
wouldn't be in this dump. The great
backyard beer with your neighbor this
place 30 years they tell you to [__] off
at the end. I'm telling you, you didn't
fight for it when you had the chance.
The biggest regret of my life is that I
don't work in an insurance
company in Ohio. The privilege. You
think I like driving this Bentley? It
ruins every other car. I'm in a rental
right now. It's It's insane. It's an
Infinity. It's insane. I don't even know
how it even happens. This Infinity truck
is horrible. Be smart.
fight for these things. I'm telling you,
so many of you are not smart enough to
understand this episode. It's very hard.
It's very hard for me. How do I have a
career at
all? Rob, you're wrong. Because now I
was killed in a tunnel
by
MR6 and the MSAD. All right. All right.
You keep doing this all the time. But
you're right. I actually believe that
the happiest I've ever been is not when
I was going to Africa pretending to care
about the babies. The happiest I've ever
been was when I was in a bank with my
girlfriends and we was all talking about
who had bigger dicks. The bank or the
bankers. Which banker had the biggest
dick. That was really fun. I didn't like
Africa. It was depressing. That's
Princess Diana saying what we all know.
Before we watch the final three Tim
Dylan podcast rants, real quick, please
make sure that you're subscribed to
Jokeworld at this time. And if you're
enjoying this video, be sure to check
out Tim's new stand-up special, I'm Your
Mother, out right now on Netflix. I
think the American public, because they
have been so heavily propagandized and
lied to and have been told things that
aren't true over and over and over
again. They the idea of fame as a
concept, they distrust now. And I think
that's a good thing. They just distrust
it. They go and then people. Do you
realize how famous people get in
America? They get so famous in America.
It's not even fun anymore. It's not even
fun. The Kardashians are so famous now.
They don't even have fans anymore. No
one even likes them. They're just there.
They're fixtures. They just exist. It's
like a religion. They're just there.
It's there. And you drive by and you
look at the church, maybe you go in a
few times a year. It's just there. It's
a part of our society now. There's no
fans of these people anymore. Jake and
Logan Paul are so famous. No one loves
them anymore. And people have just
gotten tired of hating them. They're
just there. You relent. They relent. You
go, "All right, all right, fine.
That's Yeah, yeah, yeah. The card,
they're going to be the most famous
people in the world. I just got I got to
afford medicine." You succumb to it. You
and you know, you have no say in it
either. You don't really have a say in
what h you just eventually you turn
around. If you're a normal person, you
just turn around and there's a bunch of
people who are the most famous people in
the world and you don't know why. You
can't you don't know why. Every now and
then you get like a Shane Gillis who's a
generational talent, who's an amazing,
you know what I mean? Standup comedian
guy. I get it. Or you get uh even the
guy who was watching do tennis last
night, Skinner, whatever his name is. I
don't want to learn his name. I don't
care. It doesn't matter to me. I'm not
learning his name. Yanick. Yannic. I'll
blow him. I'm not learning his name. The
point is these people you watch. I
watched a guy play tennis and go, I get
it. That guy's a top. That guy's amaz
whatever. However it happened, he's
amazing. Then there's just a bunch of
people that are just the most famous
people. They're the most famous people
in the world. And you don't know why you
put a gun in your mouth. You wouldn't be
able to. And tell us why this or I don't
know. I don't know why
famous. I don't know. They were I don't
know. No one knows. So, no one knows why
some people are famous. They're just the
most famous people in the world. You
just you relent. You go, "Okay, fine.
They're just famous. You there's nothing
else to do. You would not be able to
articulate it on your deathbed with a
gun to the back of your child's head.
You couldn't even come up with a fake
reason why half of these people are
famous." So, what happens is you just
relent. But it's that culture of fame
like Russia. No, Russia's like, "We got
to just start paying people in America
that are famous to say [__] because
apparently these people will listen."
And it's like, "Yes, yes, yes. I get it.
Spread that money around. Spread that
money." But it's it's this this this
this game now of of of like fame means
not. It just isn't anything anymore. It
has it's lost all of the things that it
had. Part of the problem is that that
they come up with these movies like Snow
White, they ruin the movie and then you
have this [__] I mean, these are the
mo when actors and actresses talk, you
realize that they're the biggest losers
in the world. Now, the reason that we
can tolerate that is because we don't
know that. They read words written by
other people and all of their
appearances are carefully managed and
choreographed. But when they go off book
and they start telling us who they are,
we realize they suck and we hate them.
And that's what's really destroying
Hollywood. Sure, there's a million
reasons, but the biggest thing these
people when just given the chance
completely everything by talking and if
they would just shut their mouth. No one
is asking these people to talk. No one
is pleading with them for their opinions
on anything. No one cares. but they feel
compelled because they're watching the
people on the internet talk and get a
following being authentic or being
themselves or being some version of
themselves or whatever. That being said,
these people go, "Oh, I'll do that. I'll
weigh in." And they make a big mess and
everybody hates it. Now, let's watch
Rachel Zgler here. It's just it's it's
cocky. It's humorless. It's everything
wrong with everything. Let's watch it.
And to
everyone who hates when I win. Oh my
god. The wind victory came to the Lou in
pieces. What? And people still line up
to see her. Oh no. And I can only hope
that despite my flaws. Oh boy. And
despite my cracks and my breaks, and
there are many of
them, that at every premiere Oh boy. And
everything I do, people will wait in
line to see.
Yeah. I
mean, someone has to put her in a
cage. Someone has to put her in a cage.
I mean, there's no other way to say it.
She She should not be allowed out if
she's going to behave like this while
she has a movie out. You you you you
have to put these people in a cage. If
you are not, if you cannot keep your
mouth shut, you have to get locked in a
cage until we put a lot of money into
this film. We put a lot of money into
this film and if you cannot participate
in the promotional roll out, we're
putting you in a cage. We're locking you
in a room until you learn how to be with
all my flaws. With all my flaws, I hope
at every premiere people buy ticket.
They're all crazy. They're all
psychotic. It's insane. They're all
little Hitlers despite my flaws. I hope
at every premiere. I mean, just it's in
the They're always acting. They're not
humans. They're not people. They they
they they must be put in a cage for
their own good. For their own good.
You're not going to save Gaza. I'm not
saying she's wrong about everything she
says. I don't know what she I don't
care. But you're not going to do it.
You're just Snow White and it's fake.
you're actually not even her. She
doesn't exist. You don't have any powers
to save these people who are hurting.
And this idea that you like need to
speak up. It does. It's not. You don't.
You actually don't. You can just shut
the up. That's what I would say. I would
say the the movie is coming out now and
I put everyone in I would I would get
everyone in an office and I would say we
spent all this money on this movie Snow
White and um it's about to come out and
if if you open your
mouth at all about
Gaza, I'm going to I'm going to come and
I'm going to kill you. I'm going to come
to your house. I'm going to kill you. Do
you understand that? I'm going to come
to your house and I'll kill you. If you
talk about trans kids hanging themsel or
Gaza in the middle of the Snow White
roll out the production, Here's what I
want you to talk about. Uh, I love the
movie. It's beautiful. I What a story
and I'm so glad we get to retell it and
reintroduce it to a whole new generation
of children. And then I know you're
gonna want to say more. I know you're
gonna want to say more and and you're
gonna go, "And speaking of children,"
and I'm gonna go, "Shut up. Shut up.
Speaking of
children, shut up. No matter what
happens, no matter if we're nuked, no
matter if it takes a billion years, no
matter if aliens land, we will always,
this will always be the zenith. We'll
always just go right back to this. We
will always go back to a self-important
[__] selling cake to people before it
all goes haywire again. Before the
planet burns, before another ice age,
before the aliens come, before fog
blankets the earth, before we're all
killed, I'm telling you right now,
society will always rebuild back to
this. There's nothing else. Society will
always build back to this [__] in a
beekeeper outfit making honey. It will
always build back to this because
there's nowhere else to go. That's the
great irony here. That's the great irony
of the human experience. There's nowhere
else really to go. This is it. Every
time society gets to this, they have to
nuke us and blow up the whole thing and
we got to start again. The Samrian
tablets and the aliens land and they go,
"How about you do it this way?" And hey,
this is math and oh, cool. And then the
middle ages and oh, there's medicine.
You don't have to use the leeches. And
how about flight? You want to fly? And
then you got, "Oh, cool. A computer.
That's weird. Oh, it fits in your hand."
And then no matter what, we always get
to this. We'll always just get to this.
I like to give people little moments,
little things. I start with a color that
inspires me and I just move on from
there. A little raspberry here, some
flowers here. They're edible flowers. It
always gets This is deep place. And I
guarantee you that we've done this
before. We've been here before. We can
feel it. We know it. We've been here
before. Society will only ever get to
this. And at this point when we are
doing this, when this [__] is drinking
tea, that's when it's time to shut it
all down and start over. And each time
the aliens sit there and each time they
go, I wonder if it'll be different this
time. I wonder if they'll get to another
point this time. What happens? And every
time it's a Meghan Markle, and every
time she moves into the castle, and
every time she gets offended, every time
she leaves, and every time they go,
"Well, maybe good for her. or what you
going to do now? And then every time she
gets the deal with Spotify and Netflix,
and then every time she makes a bunch of
[__] And then every time she starts
a lifestyle brand and fires all her
employees and half of them quit cuz
she's a [__] And then every time she
ends up with this Netflix show where
she's in a beekeeper outfit and the
aliens, they're running the simulation
going, "Just one time. Just one time
we'd wonder what would happen if they
made other choices. Just one time we
wonder what would happen. Just one
time." and we go, do you think they'll
get to this point and not do this? But
every time, like clockwork, no matter
what, time doesn't matter up there. So
to us, it's billions and billions of
years. To them, it's just every day you
go to the office, you click on, is it
still this [__] Is it still the honey?
Is it still the cupcakes? Is this still
what they're doing? And every time every
time the alien sees this, every time
they see this
trailer, they just look at the other
alien and they
go and then the other alien just shakes
their head. It's non-verbal at this
point. And then they press a button and
they delete they delete the
simulation. And then they go back in the
next day. Alien's taken off his coat. He
walks into the room and they're staring
again and she goes, "Look at how much
honey we have." And they just
go and it's just a and there eventually
they'll have to give up on us.
Eventually they'll have to realize that
no matter what they do, no matter how
many chances they give us, it's just
going to be this [__] making cupcakes
and having glasses of white wine. That's
all it really is here. So guys, however
you do it,
fog, exploding, uh, cyber trucks, uh,
cars going too fast, whatever you're
going to do, nukes, drones, whatever it
you can do it until your little hearts,
uh, content, we will never not be stupid
[__] in Santa Barbara making cupcakes
for our dumb [__] friends. It's who we
are. That's who we are. That's what you
got. So, you might as well not nuke us.
You might as well not nuke us. You might
as well call the drones back and just
let this puppy percolate and maybe taste
those cupcakes because they're probably
not that bad. Don't expect too much from
us and you're not going to get it. Good
night.
Joke World. That's it. Joke World and
the world is W RLD.
That's a great uh YouTube channel, Joke
World. Check it out.